I've wrote this letter to remind myself
the reasons I'm alive
I got to reason number five
To find words that described all the times
I caught myself and realised
There are good things just ahead of me
But I know that I'm safe when I leave
When you can't speak to me
And when I can't receive
The words I know you mеan
You think can set me free
I know it's broken but a
littlе part of me thinks that I'm glad
I can go through things that make me sad
Any more, then I start to go mad
Reason that I had at number one
Was I like to
Like the feeling of becoming numb
I can't choose
Speak to me
And when I can't receive
The words I know you mean
You think can set me free
It's better you leave me be
Reason that I had at number one
Was I like to
Know the feeling well of being loved
Then number two
I like the feeling of becoming numb
I can't choose
Which one I prefer because you can't
Reason that I had at number one
Was I like to
Know the feeling well of being loved
Then number two
I like the feeling of becoming numb
I can't choose
Which one I prefer because you can't